[Music]
Your vehicle has been damaged in an accident. Don't
worry, here are the steps in the reimbursement motor
vehicle claim settlement process.
Take your damaged car to the garage
and Selfe app website
[Music]
and you will receive the surveyor details and the
survey will be conducted within 24 working hours. Based on
all the required documents and the estimator, the
surveyor will provide provisional approval to start the repair work.
After the repair, based on the documents and other
verification, the surveyor
will confirm the admissibility of the claim. Submit the repair
bill and other necessary documents, if
any, to the surveyor for processing the claim.
After submitting the required documents, the
claim will be processed within seven working days. The
claim
status will remain 'Claim Under Process' throughout the process. Once the
claim is processed, the
policyholder will
receive an SMS or email confirming the payment details. The
documents required to complete the hassle-free claim process are as follows
[Music]
Live
Smart with Reliance General Insurance with 24/7 support from Reliance General Insurance